

SUCHANUCH NARKTHONG

Software Engineering, Burapha University

CONTACT



+66 91 616 3110



aewizlies



Suchanuch.aew@gmail.com



66/259, Aspire Erawan Prime, Sukhumvit Rd., Paknam subdistrict, Muang district, Samut Prakan, 10270.

SKILLS

Proficient Analyze

Management Intermediate

Document Expert

Design (UX) Intermediate

English Good

PROGRAMS













PERSONAL INFORMATION

I am 26 years old and you can call me "Aew". I am interested in technology and analysis about website and application. I would love to talk with many people to learn about their characteristic. I have knowledge of management and problem solving skills.

In addition, I can be able to work under pressure and meet tight schedules. Including alert, aggressive and willing to work hard.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) in Software Engineering, 2018, Burapha University. GPA. 3.55

EXPERIENCE

@Piesoft Co., Ltd. (2018-2019)

Responsibility: Gathering user requirements, analyze requirements, find suppliers, create UX design of front-end and back-end, create UML diagram, create documents (relate project), test and train about websites and applications, and organize activities (relate project such as website or/and application launch events, press conference of public, etc.).

@Ayodia ROP(2019-2020)

Responsibility: Gathering user requirements, analyze requirements, create document (relate project), and test website and application.

@ITP Asia Co., Ltd. (2020-2022)

Responsibility: Gathering user requirements, analyze requirements, find suppliers, create UX design of front-end and back-end, create UML diagram, create documents (relate project), test and websites and applications



BURAPHA UNIVERSITY, CHON BURI, THAILAND

OFFICIAL TRANSCRIPT

Name MISS SUCHANUCH NARKTHONG

Faculty of Informatics

Date of Birth April 6, 1996

Date of Admission August 13, 2014

Date of Graduation June 15, 2018

Student No. 57160713

Nationality Thai

Major Subject Software Engineering

Minor Subject -

Degree Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)

Date of	Leaving June 15, 2018		Dis	tinction				
Course N	io. Title of Course	Cr. Gr		Course No	A STATE OF THE OWNER OF THE PARTY OF THE PAR	r. Gr	SOCON.	
1000	1st. Semester, 2014			888334	Data Communication and Computer Networks for	3	B+	
302101		2	B+		Software Engineering	2	A	
850104		1	A	888351	Team Software Development Process	1	A	
888101		3	В	888352	Team Software Development Process Laboratory	3	В	
888111		3	A	888354	Web Engineering and Contemporary Technology	3	A	
888131		2	B+	888363	Software Testing and Quality Assurance	J	11	
888141		3	A		2nd. Semester, 2016	2	C+	
	Engineering			309103	Marine Science	3	B+	
888142		1	A	887330	Application Development for Mobile Devices	3	В	
	Engineering Laboratory	3	C+	888321	Software Project Management Open Source Methodology and Business Model	3	В	
999042		3	CT	888353		3	В	
	2nd. Semester, 2014	•		888355	Software Metrics	3	B+	
402403			A B+	888364	Software Design and Architecture	3	В	
885101		3		888491	Special Topics in Software Engineering I	3	B+	
888102		3	B+	888492	Special Topics in Software Engineering II	5		
888103		3	A		1st. Semester, 2017	6	Α	
888143		3	A	888418	Cooperative Education	U	Λ	
888144		1	A	111	2nd. Semester, 2017	3	B+	
20011	Laboratory	3	A	888414	Laws and Ethics for Software Engineers	1	A	
888145		3	В	888417	Software Engineering Seminar	3	51 1700561 10 W	
999043	를 받는 것 같다. 그는 그들은 경기를 받는 것을 하는 것이 되었다면 없는 것이 되었다면 하는 것이 없는 것이다. 그렇게 되었다면 없는 것이 없는 것이 없는 것이다. 그렇게 되었다면 없는 것이 없는			888419	Software Engineering Project	3		
	1st. Semester, 2015	2	B+	888482	IT Enterprise Architecture			
423321		3	B+		Total Number of Credits Earned	138		
885201		3	A		Cumulative Grade Point Average	3.5	5	
888204		3	B+	1	Transcript Closed			
888205	Statistics and Empirical Methods for Software Engineering	,	В					
888246		3	A		Samaw mignest			
888247		3	A		(Ms. Saowance Samransuk)			
888248		· Y-	A		Registrar			
000240	Laboratory		1	,	Date Issued July 5, 2018			
888271	Data Structure and Algorithms for Software	3	B+	1				
000271	Engineering							
	2nd. Semester, 2015							
228102	Art of Speaking and Presentation	1/3	B+	十二				
228202	Academic Article and Research Writing	3	A					
888212	Software Requirement Engineering and	3	A					
	Documentation /	1111			The first that the same of the			
888213	Software Requirement Engineering and	\ 1	Α					
000001	Documentation Laboratory Software Engineering Approach to Human	3	В					
888231	Computer Interaction							
888232	Database Systems and Design	3	В					
888249	Software Development Training Camp	1	A	600				
888281	Computer Architecture and Organization for	. 3	B+	/				
	Software Engineering			Service Control		1		
	1st. Semester, 2016	1						
309103	Marine Science	2	F					
678101	Basic Knowledge of General Law	3	В	1016				
888333	Operating System for Software Engineering	3	В	1				
000333	Operating by stem for both that Disgritter				DOWN CHALLAND OPICIDIAL SIGNATURE			